

+62812 9125 4913 muh.miftah.firdaus@gmail.com

## SKILLS

Laravel Codeigniter MySQL Javascript Jquery Git

#### **PERSONAL SKILLS**

Diligent
Discipline
Organized
Time management
Fast learner
Motivated

## LANGUAGES

Bahasa Indonesia

# MUHAMMAD MIFTAH FIRDAUS

## FULL STACK DEVELOPER

## **ABOUT**

I have 4+ years experience as Full Stack Developer with strong passion to explore new things. Im familiar with Laravel, Codeigniter, HTML, Jquery, Javascript, Git and MySQL. Currently im interested and learning about Clean Code, Unit Test, Golang and CI/CD. I wanna collaborate, contribute and apply my knowledge for continuous improvement to your company.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### PT. TELKOM SATELIT INDONESIA

Full Stack Developer | December 2018 - Now

- Developing Mantools Backend is assurance system for maintenance disbursement. Disbursement integration with Midtrans and Linkaja.
- Developing Finance Service Delivery is assurance system for project disbursement
- Developing Restful API One Stop Fulfillment is API for project fulfillment.
- Daily Scrum all team.

#### **FREELANCE**

Full Stack Developer | Oct 2017 - March 2020

- Developing sparring sport platform AYO Indonesia.
- Developing admin panel online shop Farsiloon.
- Developing Restful API e-commerce, integrate with Linkaja and Alfacart -DAV

PT. PRAWATHIYA KARSA PRADIPTHA Full Stack Developer | Apr 2016 - Oct 2017

- Developing Beyond Technology for call center.
- Collaborate with Tech Lead and other Developer.

DIVISION DATA & IT BPSDM MINISTRY OF PUBLIC WORK & HOUSING INDONESIA

IT Staff | Aug 2015 - Mar 2016

• Troubleshoot IT problem.

### **EDUCATION**

BACHELOR OF SYSTEM COMPUTER
University of Gunadarma | 2010 - 2014
GPA 3.11